BABYMONSTER will turn the whole world into a dance party.
Welcome to the special Idol Party.
We'll now begin a dance initiation to find out BABYMONSTER's 'CHOOM' skills.
We ask the members to let loose and take over the dance floor.
[The first song rings in the start of the party]
[One by one, the music takes over BABYMONSTER]
[Who will open the first stage?]
[RORA taking the stage gracefully]
Doesn't this seem like that thing?
Merry-Go-Round.
[Who's stepping up to the stage next?]
[RUKA go! RUKA go!]
[Sloth? No no]
[I'm hipster RURU today]
[The next dancer summoned by DJ RORA is?]
[Come on up ASA]
[I'm owning this party]
[Audience satisfaction 417%]
[ASA brings cute, sexy, hip, the full package]
[Calling up the next player]
[No way AHYEON just entered Idol Party]
[Light and breezy grooooove]
[How is she literally a dancing peach?]
[Soft and cute]
What is this song?
Shouldn't CHIQUITA dance to this?
[Pitching ideas] Do the robot.
[Carefully taking the stage]
[Like a doll straight out of a music box]
Wow, you have long arms!
[Long-arms PHARITA's party time]
[You all know the main character shows up last]
[Unnis going wild over the maknae's entrance]
[Crowd-favorite maknae takes over]
[CHIQUITA is pure fun in human form]
[BABYMONSTER brought the real dance party energy]
Keep going.
The star of today's Idol Party and BABYMONSTER's dance queen.
The star of today's Idol Party and BABYMONSTER's dance queen. [Dance queen?]
Please give RORA a huge round of applause. [Me?]
Please give RORA a huge round of applause. [What?]
I must be the star of the party!
[Congratulate me!]
[Congratulations — but why RORA?]
[Why RORA became the dance queen] [A stage set in front of the feast table]
[The first person to dance on stage]
[Becomes the star of the party!]
[*Unfortunately, ASA danced at the back instead of on the stage]
I should've gone on stage...
Close one ASA.
I should've become the dance queen.
[How does it feel to be the dance queen?]
It's such an honor.
Thinking about getting showered with love from the members
makes me so happy.
Congratulations RORA.
[RORASA overflowing with celebration]
[Look at her face lol] [Forced congratulations]
[What kind of details do you focus on when you dance?]
When I dance,
I think about making the moves precise,
that's a given.
Something our team prioritizes is
facial expressions or attitude.
The vibe!
That's important.
I think you're right.
Our music has a lot of different genres,
so we try to have an attitude that fits each song.
- On stage.
- That's right.
[Stage detail tip for performing with straight hair]
[Flip your hair to show off your face] I use my hair as much as possible.
[Making the hair dance too]
RORA, you are the dance queen.
[Show us! Show us!]
[No big deal]
[I'm the dance queen]
[That's our dance queen RORA]
[That's our dance queen RORA] You did so good.
[Give me a high-five]
Let's move on.
Since we're on the topic of dance,
I want to talk more about the stage.
We perform on stage all the time.
I think it's really important for us
to make little changes and switch it up
to keep showing our new sides.
I think gestures are important.
And speaking of our dance queen,
[Nervous] Yes?
Her gestures improved so much.
She does things like this.
[Compilation of dance queen's legendary gestures] Sometimes she goes natural.
[Compilation of dance queen's legendary gestures]
[Compilation of dance queen's legendary gestures] She does this too.
I can't compete with AHYEON though.
[Performance mastermind AHYEON]
[No denying it]
[Shy] No, no.
Your visuals have been on another level these days.
You're so pretty.
Did I do a good job?
[I approve your comment]
[Cue the fanfare] [Hehe]
[What's going on?!]
AHYEON is dismissed,
AHYEON is dismissed, and may go home now.
[Happy baby peach is clocking out first]
[Members are in disbelief]
[Nothing gets AHYEON dancing like clocking out]
[Once the star of the party was decided, BABYMON spotted something]
[Secret clock-out mission delivered behind the party star's back!]
[Complete the hidden mission the dance queen noticing, and clock out right away!]
- Get the dance queen to copy your dance move
- Hol
[Asking for a compliment naturally]
[Smoothly got a thumbs-up]
[Dazed members and one excited chipmunk]
Don't go.
The dance queen commands!
The dance queen was never real!
Only clocking out exists!
I'm leaving!
I love you Spotify.
Bye.
I'm clocking out.
[Cool exit]
I want to go too...
[In betrayal] I'm not doing anything to you!
[No...] You have to!
[Let's calm down and move on]
[RORA is the dance queen — is there anything you think you're the queen of?]
Me.
I'm good at balancing,
so I have good core strength.
That's why I'd like to battle the dance queen.
[Nervous] What kind of battle?
What kind of battle!
[ASA called for a battle] Come on out.
[I demand a balance face-off!] You know this game, right?
Let's try it.
[This is fun]
If you lose, you can't clock out.
[Entertained]
I have good core strength!
I'm wearing heels today though.
[Battle start!]
[Cue the fanfare]
[Ta-da!]
[Success!]
[I got fooled again]
ASA is dismissed, and may go home now.
Thank you everyone.
[I'll be off then]
My mission was to
high-five the dance queen RORA
three times.
[Shocked]
[ASA the genius]
This isn't fair at all!
Then use your brain!
[While the maknaes bicker, ASA is clocking out]
[The party carries on — what are you all the queen of?]
What are you the queen of?
I'm not telling you.
I guess she doesn't want to go home.
What am I the queen of?
You're the queen of eating.
[Can't deny that]
[Urgent report — CHIQUITA's only thinking about clocking out!]
[Revealing the missions the members are stressing over]
- Get the dance queen to copy your dance move
- Hold hands with the dance queen and do a couple dance
- Get the dance queen to admit "You're the
All she can think about is going home.
My favorite Korean word is
clock out!
[The sound of employees everywhere agreeing]
You can be the queen of clocking out!
Clock-out queen!
I'm the queen of twerking.
[Ohhh]
[Show us! Show us!]
Since the dance queen is next to me,
I'd like to do it with her.
[Dance with me]
[RUKA wants to clock out too] Is this to find out who's better at shaking it?
Show us!
[We'll do it] On three, two, one.
Okay.
Together! [Not budging]
[Pleading hands]
[Desperate] Together.
[Desperate] [This is funny]
[RUKA's wish is to collab with the dance queen]
[Should I dance... or not?]
Dance with me!
[Having too much fun teasing her unni]
[Wants it so bad] Dance with me.
What do I get if I dance with you?
I'll treat you to a meal.
[A deal worthy of the foodie baby]
[Twerking 3rd attempt]
[Dancing together at last!]
[Cue the fanfare]
[Cue the fanfare] [I did it!]
RUKA is dismissed, and may go home now. [Bitter...]
Thank you.
[Party star has accepted her fate] Go ahead.
[RURU is clocking out]
[Only TATAz are left...] It's just us two.
No, no.
I'm leaving first.
[The party seems a little empty] This feels a little lonely.
Next up is Dance Charades.
The members must guess the keyword by watching BABYMONSTER's dance queen RORA dance.
The thing is...
They're both foreigners...
Exactly.
I have to play Charades with two Thai members...
Then just keep dancing.
I'm working out today.
[Let's try it!]
[Time limit: 3 minutes]
[The one who gets the most right answers]
[from RORA's dances wins!]
[Go!]
[*1st Question: Popping turtle]
[*1st Question: Popping turtle] Robot!
[*1st Question: Popping turtle] Game!
[*1st Question: Popping turtle] Character!
[*1st Question: Popping turtle] Popping!
[Yes!]
[And then...]
[Sloth!]
[Not that]
[RORA is not holding back]
[TATAz not catching on]
What is this!
What are you doing?
Plane!
Turtle.
[Yes! That one!]
[Put them together!]
Popping
Popping dance
Popping dance turtle.
[Correct!]
[Furious] What?
What even is that?
[Oh...!]
[You're running out of time!]
[Oh right!]
[*2nd Question: Duck doing fan service while waacking]
Idol... waacking...
I should give up.
Duck doing idol waacking.
[Almost there]
Uh...
Fan service!
[There you go!]
[PHARITA grabbed the chance first]
Fan service!
Fan service! While waacking!
[The answer's basically out there...!]
Chicken!
[The chance goes to CHIQUITA] What was it?
[Already forgot it]
Fan greeting.
[Isn't it fan greeting?]
I just heard PHARITA say it...
[But I forgot]
[Yay]
Fan greeting!
Guess not.
[Back to PHARITA]
Duck doing fan service while waacking.
[Correct!]
[PHARITA killed it!]
Next one!
[Time's up]
I didn't get a single one.
Wow, PHARITA is so good.
[Since CHIQUITA didn't get a right answer]
[Bonus chance is granted]
Okay.
[Tired...] I don't need this bonus chance.
[Lol]
[Then PHARITA should give the question!]
[Will TATAz be able to do well?]
[It's CHIQUITA's time!] I won't even attempt to answer.
It's fun to give the question, try it.
[Question: Robot powered off while dancing]
Dancing...
[I'm gonna get it right!] Don't say it!
[Passionate CHIQUITA] Okay...
"Mon Tue Wed Thu Fri Sat let's all get lost".
[Dancing is correct!]
[How should I explain 'powered off'...]
Sigh... this is hard...
[Announcement] I don't need to go home.
[Lol]
CHIQUITA doesn't really use this word. [Powered off]
Then how am I supposed to guess?!
[Trying a different question!]
[Checked the question]
[Question: Nine-tailed fox serving ending fairy]
TAEYANG sunbaenim...?
[Where did our sunbaenim come from?]
[Game that makes you think of your sunbaenim]
[Let's try it again]
Aegyo!
Last!
Ending fairy!
In Korean!
[How am I supposed to know that?]
Ending fairy!
[Next word: nine-tailed fox] There's no way CHIQUITA knows this...
[How am I supposed to know that x2]
[How am I supposed to know that x2] Just try it.
Take a look at the answer.
[What is it?]
Oh, we're doomed.
[Lol]
This will be impossible.
You take a look too CHIQUITA.
[Finally faced the question: Nine-tailed fox serving ending fairy] What is that?
[Okay, she officially doesn't know]
I only know ending fairy.
[Dance Charades MVP is PHARITA]
[Discovered a whole new PHARITA] She was so good.
It was fun.
RORA was good at explaining.
[Not bad, right?]
Since PHARITA got the answer right,
[Present?] you get to
[Winner's privilege] do the 'CHOOM' challenge with the dance queen.
[Winner's privilege] do the 'CHOOM' challenge with the dance queen. [No present...?]
[Let's 'CHOOM'!]
[She might be able to do her mission: Hold hands with the dance queen and do a couple dance]
[It's just the two of them, yet it's flawless]
[Imagine how perfect the official performance must be]
[Listen to BABYMONSTER's 'CHOOM' on Spotify!]
['CHOOM' challenge was a success]
[But someone forgot about the clock-out mission]
That was so good.
Today's highlight! It's time to make a Spotify playlist.
[Ultimate dopamine anthem that gets me dancing]
The members who left early didn't even get to introduce their songs.
Too bad, we're the only ones who got the chance.
I chose a song called 'Trendsetter'.
It's such a great song.
I like it a lot,
and it's fun to dance to.
That's why I chose it.
[Next!]
I chose BIGBANG's 'WE LIKE 2 PARTY'.
It speaks for itself.
It's a song everyone sings along to,
which is why I chose it.
I chose Rihanna.
But,
just singing it isn't enough, right?
Do you want to dance with me?
[Oh that was smooth] Since it's 'Don't Stop The Music'?
[This isn't a mission, right?] [Is it?] [Am I being left alone?]
What kind of dance should we do?
Should we do a couple's dance?
Then you count the beat.
[Overthinking... but still a well-behaved maknae]
[PHAROz party time]
[Cue the fanfare]
[I knew it!]
PHARITA is dismissed, and may go home now.
[What was PHARITA's clock-out mission?]
[PHARITA's mission: Hold hands with the dance queen and do a couple dance]
[Oh?!]
You suggested it!
Rewind please.
[30 seconds ago] What kind of dance should we do?
[30 seconds ago] Should we do a couple's dance?
[Spoon-fed the mission] [Still stuck at work] [Clocking out thanks to RORA]
[What a combo]
[PHARITA is out!]
[Just the maknaes now] I was the best, right? Admit it!
[You're so cute CHIQUITA]
[Desperate] [Needs to hear "You're the best" to go home] Please!
Please say it, just once... [This is hilarious]
Please!
[Or else I'm biting you!] Say it!
She was pretty cute just now, right?
[Being cute isn't the issue right now] I'm the best, right?
I'll call you unni!
RORA unni!
[Forcing the mission] I was the best today, right? Say it.
For BABYMONSTER's 'CHOOM' comeback, Spotify has prepared a heartfelt present.
I don't think I can trust Spotify's presents anymore!
[Same...]
[RORA's reaction game is strong]
They're real presents!
[Real cheering]
[Real presents have arrived]
[Trading clock-out for a gift] You got this present because I didn't let you go home!
[I'm happy now] Okay, I like this.
[Unboxing time]
[Lol]
[Gifts from Spotify that'll come in handy during 'CHOOM' promotions]
ASA will be really envious of this.
[CHIQUITA cheers]
[Spotify gift you can't wait to dig into] What's this?
[Touched]
It's a letter!
BABYMONSTER got me dancing all day long.
Maybe 'CHOOM' is just that good.
Spotify wholeheartedly supports
BABYMONSTER's 'CHOOM' era.
[Manifesting success for 'CHOOM']
[Final event of Idol Party! Group photo time]
Please rise from your seats.
[Cozy two-person group shot] A group photo?
[Cozy two-person group shot]
[Forever-bickering maknae duo]
[Many Spotify listeners joined us]
[to celebrate the dancing machine, dance queen RORA]
[Role of many Spotify listeners]
[RORA teasing CHIQUITA till the end] Thank you.
I was so touched
that you stayed with me until the very end.
It's fine, it's fine.
I'm not done.
I didn't realize my younger member cared about me this much.
- I didn't realize my younger member cared about me this much.
- Younger member.
[Ha...] She said she'd call me RORA unni from today.
[Love their playful bickering]
How does it feel to stay until the end?
I didn't know I would still be here.
[Lol]
It's just so...
[They all left]
I'm the only one here...
[Hmph]
[Hmph] You're here.
I'm the star of the party!
[Oh right, I was only thinking about clocking out...]
Right, what were you again?
The dance queen.
[CHIQUITA failed her mission, do you want to guess what it was?]
[Should I let her go... or not...]
What could it be?
Just say I'm the best.
[Not even hiding the mission lol]
You're the best at eating.
[Irritated...]
[Still not over teasing CHIQUITA] You're the best at eating in our team.
[Doing ASA's mission] Let's do three high-fives!
[And PHARITA's mission] Let's do a couple dance too.
[Never doing CHIQUITA's mission] This isn't my mission.
[Can you do it now?] Say "you're the best."
[Teasing time is over] You're the best.
[Did you hear that?!]
[Cue the fanfare]
[CHIQUITA can finally clock out!]
[Okay, but you gotta hug me] CHIQUITA is dismissed, and may go home now.
Wasn't my mission the hardest? [Why aren't you hugging me...?]
[We thought it was the easiest...]
[It was basically the theme of this party...]
[Upset over not getting a hug]
It's not something RORA says to me often.
[Why... should I...?]
[Let's do a make-up hug]
[Forever the funniest duo]
[Lol]
[Bye CHIQUITA]
I'm finally clocking out.
My favorite word.
[Clock out]
When this started,
my side was nice and warm.
Now it feels empty.
I'm happy to be here till the end.
[Should we wrap up with a dance?]
[RORA never says no]
[Watch more BABYMONSTER content on K-Pop ON! Video Podcast]